<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_era_immersive_hud"><text>Era's Immersive HUD</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_title"><text>Era's Immersive HUD</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_help"><text>Toggle your HUD with a single hotkey. Each element below can be set to Always show, Always hide, or Toggle with Hotkey (hidden until you press the key). Bind your hotkey first as it is unbound by default.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_sect_reveals"><text>Reveal triggers temporarily show an element when its visibility mode (set below) is "Toggle with Hotkey". Setting an element to "Always hide" overrides its reveal triggers and keeps it hidden.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_sect_modes"><text>Set how each HUD element behaves: Always show, Always hide, or Toggle with Hotkey (hidden until you press the toggle hotkey). "Always hide" takes precedence over the auto-reveal triggers above, except for the on-damage and new-status reveals.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_era_ihud_mode_show"><text>Always show</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_era_ihud_mode_hide"><text>Always hide</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_era_ihud_mode_key"><text>Toggle with Hotkey</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_toggle_key"><text>Toggle HUD hotkey</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_toggle_key_desc"><text>The key that shows or hides the HUD. Pressing it flips every element set to "Toggle with Hotkey" between shown and hidden. Elements set to "Toggle with Hotkey" start hidden each time a save loads.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_toggle_modifier"><text>Hotkey modifier</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_toggle_modifier_desc"><text>An optional modifier (Shift, Ctrl, or Alt) that must be held together with the toggle hotkey for it to fire.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_auto_hide"><text>Auto-hide after showing</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_auto_hide_desc"><text>When enabled, toggling the HUD with the hotkey automatically hides it again after the "reveal duration" set below (in seconds).</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_reveal_duration"><text>Reveal duration (seconds)</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_long_press"><text>Long-press hold time (seconds needed to lock)</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_long_press_desc"><text>Hold the toggle hotkey for at least this long to pin the HUD on.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pin_enabled"><text>Long-press to lock (pin) the HUD on</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pin_enabled_desc"><text>When enabled, holding the toggle hotkey (for the duration set below) pins the HUD on, ignoring the auto-hide timer until you tap the hotkey again.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_show_lock"><text>Show "locked" indicator when pinned</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_show_lock_desc"><text>While the HUD is pinned on, show a small lock icon on the bottom left so you know it is pinned and ignoring the auto-hide timer.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_reveal_inventory"><text>Show health and statuses while in inventory</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_reveal_inventory_desc"><text>While your inventory or PDA is open, show BHS health HUD and status effects.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_messages_in_inventory"><text>Show PDA messages while in inventory</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_messages_in_inventory_desc"><text>While your inventory or PDA is open, show the bottom-left news pop-ups (pickups, tips, task updates, faction messages).</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_bhs_on_damage"><text>Show health when taking damage</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_bhs_on_damage_desc"><text>When you take a hit or psy damage the BHS hud will show.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_bhs_keep_while_hurt"><text>Keep panel shown while hurt</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_bhs_keep_while_hurt_desc"><text>Requires "Show health when taking damage". When damage reveals the BHS panel, keep it on screen for as long as you stay hurt (health or psy not full), ignoring the auto-hide timer. You can still hide it manually with the toggle hotkey.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_stamina_on_drain"><text>Show stamina bar when sprinting</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_stamina_on_drain_desc"><text>While the BHS panel is hidden, reveal just the stamina bar once you have spent about 10% of your stamina, and keep it shown until it refills. The BHS panel still shows its stamina bar as normal when it is revealed.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_radiation_on_present"><text>Show radiation bar when irradiated</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_radiation_on_present_desc"><text>While the radiation bar is hidden, reveal it whenever you are irradiated, and keep it shown until your radiation returns to zero. Might not work well with different BHS texture mods.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_statuses_on_new"><text>Show status effects when a new one appears</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_statuses_on_new_desc"><text>When a new status-effect icon appears (radiation, bleeding, hunger, a food/med buff, etc.) briefly reveal the status-effect bar, then auto-hide it after the reveal duration.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_weapon_out"><text>Show ammo when weapon is drawn</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_weapon_out_desc"><text>While the ammo and weapon HUD is hidden, reveal it whenever a weapon is in your hands, and hide it again when you holster.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_mag_not_full"><text>Show ammo when magazine isn't full</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_mag_not_full_desc"><text>While the ammo and weapon HUD is hidden, reveal it whenever your equipped weapon's magazine is not full, so you can see your remaining rounds, and hide it again once you reload to full. Might work weird with magazine mods.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_on_fire"><text>Show ammo briefly after firing</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_on_fire_desc"><text>While the ammo and weapon HUD is hidden, reveal it for the reveal duration each time you fire (even if the magazine is still full), then auto-hide it again.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo"><text>Ammo and weapon HUD</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_ammo_desc"><text>The weapon icon, ammo count, and fire-mode indicator.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_minimap"><text>Minimap</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_radiation"><text>Radiation bar</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_radiation_desc"><text>The radiation bar above the stamina bar.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_bhs"><text>Body-health panel (BHS)</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_body_health_desc"><text>BHS and psy health bar.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_statuses"><text>Status effect icons</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_status_desc"><text>The status-effect icons such as hunger, thirst, radiation, bleeding, etc.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_messages"><text>PDA messages</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_messages_desc"><text>The bottom-left news pop-ups (pickups, tips, task updates, faction messages).</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_notification"><text>PDA notification icon</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_pda_notification_desc"><text>The small notification icon on the right that shows when a new PDA message arrives.</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_companion"><text>Companion list</text></string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_era_ihud_companion_desc"><text>The on-screen companion list (health and distance) shown when you have squad members.</text></string>
</string_table>
